{
    "id": "8c4184e4d4384a11915336db2eaf49ef",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The older I get, ……………… I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the happy",
                "the happier",
                "happier",
                "happy"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b2f30ffd71f41feaed9317d9bac4ea7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your accent is ………………… in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worst",
                "the worst",
                "worse"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "892682a2c56242578b6f0c80c21d0145"
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed an extra night so that I …………………. see Ann.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc5f34d408154e0a89ea581622e113cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "While I ………………. a shower, I slipped on the floor.",
            "description": "The main verb is in the past tense, so we need a past tense in the subordinate clause as well. ",
            "answers": [
                "am having",
                "was having",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ffe22a64850143f9bed4a705c7925cd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man …………………. she married was an old friend of mine.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, that can be used instead of whom.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "68ea4e9ca1b746bb83d24b8049d210eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ……………….. I live is very small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2feae7c4f0e4882bd2b27c86f389b22"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is the girl ……………….. works with my sister.",
            "description": "Here the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause and hence we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "751f0412e1204b638a8d06b4eb269a03"
        },
        {
            "question": "The road is getting ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more and more steep",
                "steeper and steeper",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "50c3f5d5f0ef4a06ace1bb38d99c60ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got …………………. than I used to have.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. Lesser is now only used in expressions like 'the lesser of the two evils'.",
            "answers": [
                "less energy",
                "lesser energy",
                "least energy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ffcffde0a6e441d89f5e227bb9d9454"
        },
        {
            "question": "She likes music, and ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so I",
                "so do I",
                "I so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a33be5d279de4e3090a7f7b1177c9e79"
        }
    ]
}